When the last angel falls, the fight for mankind begins.
Legion is a action, fantasy, horror film directed by Scott Stewart.
When God loses faith in humankind, he sends his legion
of angels to bring on the Apocalypse.
Humanity's only hope for survival lies in a group of strangers trapped in
an out-of-the-way, desert diner with the Archangel Michael.
Michael, played by Paul Bettany.
Bob Hanson, played by Dennis Quaid.
Jeep Hanson, played by Lucas Black.
Sandra Anderson, played by Kate Walsh.
Kyle Williams, played by Tyrese Gibson.
Charlie, played by Adrianne Palicki.
Legion is a 2010 American action horror film directed by Scott
Stewart and co-written by Stewart and Peter Schink.
The film stars Paul Bettany, Lucas Black, Tyrese Gibson,
Adrianne Palicki, Kate Walsh, and Dennis Quaid.
Sony Pictures Worldwide Acquisitions Group acquired most of the film's worldwide distribution rights,
releasing the film theatrically in North America on January 22, 2010 through Screen Gems.
A story of the Second Coming, Legion follows a group of people as they attempt to
protect an infant savior from angels and the possessed in an apocalypse.
Legion was released to negative critical reception but was a success at the
box office, earning over $67 million on a $26 million budget.
A television series titled Dominion, set 25 years after the film, premiered on
the American cable television network Syfy on June 19, 2014.
The film explores themes of angel, supernatural, diner, religion, apocalypse.
The tone is uplifting and dark.